<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
	<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_v">
        <text>Convert to soft wrap.</text>
</string>


<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_v_desc">
        <text>This key bind should be a hard wrap, however there is a way to get a very similar behavior as a softwrap. This may need to be unchecked if the key misbehaves.</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_enable">
        <text>Enable</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_bind">
        <text>Wrapper key</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_geiger">
        <text>Due to the way the geiger counter script works the mode and modifier of this key cannot be chosen. It will instead be bound to both single press and single press with shift held.</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_toggle">
        <text>This key is curently set to be held down in the Anomaly settings, if you would like to use it with this system it will need to be changed to be a toggle.</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_modkey">
        <text>This wrap will be disabled if left bound to shift, alt or control.</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_bind_modifier">
        <text>Cannot be bound to a modifier!\n</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_bind_conflict">
        <text>Cannot set two wraps to the same key/mode/modifier combo.\n</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_too_many_redirects">
        <text>Hard wrap limit reached, no more keys to use as redirects. See Readme.\n</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_bind_toggle">
        <text>Disabled due to key not being set as toggle in Anomal settings.\n</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrap_about_text">
        <text>MCM Key Wrapper is a utility that allows Anomaly engine keys to be bound as MCM Key Binds.\n\n It does this by "wrapping" the keys in a bit of code that ridirects key press event.\n There are two types of redirects used by the wrappers: soft and hard.\n\n Soft redirects work on keys that are only listened for by scripts, not the engine. They work by lying to the scripts about what keys do what. You can enable an unlimited number of wraps that use a soft redirect.\n\n Hard redirects work by rebinding the key to something obscure like the Yen key and then triggering that key when the MCM Keybind is triggered. There are only a limited number of these obscure keys available, 17 by default, this places a hard limit on the number of wraps that can be enabled that use hard redirects. If you exceed that number the extra wraps will be disabled. See the readme for more details.\n\n\n There is an experimental third type of wrap that can be either a hard wrap or a soft wrap. When set as a soft wrap a script is setup to emulate the engine behavior of the key bind. This may not be an exact match and you may need to set these to be a hard wrap for compatablity</text>
</string>

<string id="ui_mcm_mcm_key_wrapper_about_unbind_disabled">
        <text>Unbind disabled wraps</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_mcm_key_wrapper_about_unbind_disabled_desc">
        <text>Cleans up conflict list. Cannot be undone.</text>
</string>


<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrap_about">
        <text>About</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_virtual">
        <text>This is a soft wrap and does not count toward the limited number of hard wraps that you can enable.</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_redirect">
        <text>This is a hard wrap and you can only have a limited number of them enabled at one time.</text>
</string>
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper">
        <text>Key Wrapper</text>
</string>

<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_wraps_were_disabled">
        <text>Wraps were disabled:\n\n</text>
</string>	
<string id="ui_mcm_key_wrapper_not_level_present">
        <text>Wraps are only accessible in a loaded game.</text>
</string>	
	

	
</string_table>
